<?xml version="1.0"?>
<cv>
    <personal>
        <firstname>Rodrigo</firstname>
        <lastname>Dias</lastname>
        <address>5, Paymal House, London E1 3HR</address>
        <email>rodrigo.pitta@gmail.com</email>
        <dob>10/09/1976</dob>
    </personal>
    <overview>
        I have moved to the UK in 2007 coming from Portugal.
        I know a lot of frameworks and have good managerial skills.

        Over the years I've been involved with a range of projects in a diverse set of industries.
        Highlights include getting my hand dirty in the guts and at the edges of a foreign exchange trading system,
        designing and implementing a social network from scratch, refactoring a number of websites to achieve
        impressive increases in performance, traffic and revenue, and designing and implementing the public APIs
        for one of the leading big data companies in the world as well as getting involved with some of the core
        aspects of their platform.

        I enjoy designing and building innovative software solutions. My motivation comes from solving tough problems
        in efficient and cost-effective ways. I try not to tie myself to particular development environments,
        programming languages or technologies, and light up at the prospect of learning something new. I'm always
        looking for opportunities to put cutting edge technology through its paces in appropriate situations, and
        also get great satisfaction from building rock solid systems build on well-established components.

        What I look for in the work I do is a challenge, and that can come in many forms. Sometimes it's breaking new
        ground, and other times it's taking an ageing system and formulating a plan to update it while ensuring
        continuous service and data integrity.

        My strongest skills lie in designing systems and guiding the development process, but that doesn't mean
        I won't get my head down and get involved with the code. Watching a system design become real is incredibly
        satisfying.
    </overview>
    <achievements>

    </achievements>
    <languages>
        <php scale="100"></php>
        <sql scale="85"></sql>
        <java scale="50"></java>
        <go scale="10"></go>
        <rust scale="10"></rust>
        <python scale="25"></python>
    </languages>
    <frameworks>

    </frameworks>


</cv>
